Inventory of the Francis P. Lee Papers 1727-1866
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- Correspondence and Legal Papers.
  - S[arah] A. C. Lee, Camden, South Carolina, to Thomas B. Lee, February 24, 1860., 2 copies. ALS. (Box-folder 3:23)
    Discusses inheritance of family property; has lost money; children are well.
  - Power of attorney - Sarah Ann C. Lee to John Clement, April 3, 1860., 4 pages. ADS. (Box-folder 3:24)
  - Eliza Lee, Society Hill, to Em[ma Lee?] ,April 12, 1866., 4 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 3:25)
    Describes her trip; family news.
  - Barnwell S. Stuart to "wife" [Emma Lee?], June-August 1866., 5 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 3:26)
    Describes his trip to New Jersey and Philadelphia; sends news of the Cooper family.
  - W. Morris Cooper to [Sarah Ann Cooper Lee?], n.d., 2 pages. ALS. Fragment. (Box-folder 3:27)
    Discusses dealings of Ralph Cooper and W. Morris Cooper's attempts to protect himself and the recipient.
  - J. Crois, N[ew] Bruns[wic]k, New Jersey, to Francis P. Lee, Camden, New Jersey, May 26., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 3:28)
    Asks him to visit on his way to the convention; Catherine married yesterday.
  - C[harles] C. Gaskell to "cousin" [Sarah Ann Cooper Lee], n.d., 7 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 3:29)
    Concerns business affairs managed by Gaskell.
  - ? to Charles C. Gaskell, Camden, N[ew] Jersey ,n.d., 2 pages. L. (Box-folder 3:30)
    Sends Mrs. Sarah Ann C. Lee's bank stock of various Philadephia banks.
  - F[rancis] P. L[ee], Savannah, to Sarah C. Lee, Camden, South Carolina, April 14., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 3:31)
    Read prayers; the bishop repeated his sermon and administered confirmation to nine persons.
  - F[rancis] P. Lee to Sarah C. Lee, Camden, South Carolina, n.d., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 3:32)
    Went to House of Representatives and listened to [?] McCarthy's speech against Calhoun not carried.
  - [Francis P. Lee?] to "My Dear Brother," n.d., 4 pages. L. Fragment. (Box-folder 3:33)
    Recalls their parting; describes his studies at Princeton.
  - Letter drafts of Francis P. Lee, n.d., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:34)
    Drafts probably written during his time at Princeton, one on back of last page of letter from Barlow Mason.
  - Miscellaneous letters by Sarah Ann Cooper Lee, on business matters, n.d., 3 letters. (Box-folder 3:35)
  - Sermon by Rt. Rev. Bishop. [N. H.] Cobbs., 1 item. Ms. Vol. (Box-folder 3:36)
  - Interrogatories to Ralph V. M. Cooper, an insolvent debtor., 1 page. AD. (Box-folder 3:37)
  - Francis P. Lee, memos of trustees and faculty and others associated with South C[arolina] College., 2 items. DS. (Box-folder 3:38)
  - "Slices of Bacon.", 6 pages. MsV. (Box-folder 3:39)
    Probably notes on readings.
  - Francis P. Lee sermons and writing fragments., 20 items. (Box-folder 3:40)
  - Francis P. Lee sermon notes., 91 items. (Box-folder 3:41)
  - Francis P. Lee travel notes., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:42)
  - Francis P. Lee visiting lists., 3 items. (Box-folder 3:43)
  - Unidentified letter fragments, n.d., 4 items. (Box-folder 3:44)
  - Francis P. Lee, "Letter Book &ca", 1829-1835., 9 pages. MsV. (Box-folder 4:1)
    Contains poems and letters to M. E. L.
  - Francis P. Lee, Book of the Church, 1838-1844., 21 pages. MsV. (Box-folder 4:2)
    Lists expenses and wages while at St. John's Church, Tallahassee, Florida, and Grace Church, Camden, South Carolina
  - Francis P. Lee, "The Advantages of Association for Literary Purposes", February 3, 1843., 32 pages. MsV. (Box-folder 4:3)
    Speech given before the DeKalb Lyceum, [Camden, South Carolina?].
  Series 2: Sermons and Essays
- Sermons and Essays.
  Often including notes on where read, discussed, or preached, and giving the numbers of the hymns used.
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #1 "First Sermon," 1833 April 29., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 4:4)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #2 "Ecclesiastes c. 1 v. 2," 1834 January 5., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 4:5)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #3 "Essay on Prayer," 1834 February 3., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 4:6)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #4 "Evidences of Love Towards God," 1834 April 2., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 4:7)
  - Francis P. Lee "Essay" #5, 1834 November 10., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 4:8)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #6, 1834 November 20., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 4:9)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #7 "Christ Our Life," 1834 December 20., 2 items. Ms. (Box-folder 4:10)
    Includes a 4 pages. revised version.
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #9 "Jewish Doctrine of a Future State," 1835 February 27., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 4:11)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #10 "John 3:14, 15," n.d., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 4:12)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #11 "Resurrection," 1835 April 27., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 4:13)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #1[2]"Justification," 1835 November 20., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 4:14)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #13 "Human Depravity," 1835 December 23., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 4:15)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #14, 1836 January 12., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 4:16)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #15 "True and False Evidences of Renovation," 1836 March 2., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 4:17)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #16 " [Ev]idences," 1836 April 21., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 4:18)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #17 "Regeneration and Renewal," 1836 May 21., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 4:19)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #20 "Burden of the World," 1836 July 8., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 4:20)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #21 "The Lusts of the Flesh," 1836 July 22., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 4:21)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #25 "Funeral," 1836 September 12., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 4:22)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #26 "Profit of Godliness," 1836 September 30., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 4:23)
  - [Francis P. Lee] Sermon #26 "Now the Days of David Drew Nigh," 1836., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 4:24)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #27 "Indecision," 1836 October 7., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 4:25)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #28 "Just Persons," 1836 October 22., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 4:26)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #29 "Christ's Victory," 1836 November 2., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 4:27)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #30 "Christ Crucified," 1836 November 11., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 4:28)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #31 "Christ Crucified," 1836 November 17., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 4:29)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #32 " The Living Sacrifice ," 1836 December 4., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 4:30)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #33 "Voice in the Wilderness," 1836 December 9., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 4:31)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #36 " Works of Dar[kness] ," 1836 December 31., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 4:32)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #38 "Christ Rejected," 1837 January 26., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 5:1)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #39 "The Progress of Sin," 1837 February 3., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 5:2)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #40 "Divine Imitation," 1837 February 9., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 5:3)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #41 "Repent!", 1837 February 24., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 5:4)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #43 "Repentance Effectual," 1837 March 8., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 5:5)
  - F[rancis] P. Lee Sermon #44 "The Condemnation," 1837 April 6., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 5:6)
  - F[ranci]s P. Lee Sermon #46 "The Sad Experiment--Life," 1837 April 29., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 5:7)
  - [Francis P. Lee] Sermon #49 "The Vine," [1837]., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 5:8)
    With pen and ink sketch of grapes and wine by [?] Drayton.
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #50 "Grace," 1837 July 1., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 5:9)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #51 "Liberty," 1837 July 3., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 5:10)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #53 "The Flesh Not Omnipotent," 1837 July 28., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 5:11)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #54 "Christian Morality," 1837 August 5., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 5:12)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #55 "Holy Baptism," 1837 August 20., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 5:13)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #57 "God's Grace," 1837 September 3., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 5:14)
  - [Francis P. Lee] Sermon #59 "Whole Duty of Man," [1837?]., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 5:15)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #61 "Charity," 1838 April 24., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 5:16)
  - [Francis P. Lee] Sermon #63 "Communion," [1838, May?]., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 5:17)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #65 "Providence in the Redemption," 1838 June 30., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 5:18)
  - [Francis P. Lee] Sermon #66 "Providence," [1838, July]., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 5:19)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #67 "The Scriptures," 1838 July 19., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 5:20)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #69 "Bondage of Sin," 1838 September 22., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 5:21)
  - [Francis P. Lee] Sermon #70 "Evidence from Miracles," [1838]., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 5:22)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #75 "Worldly Conformity," [1839] January 13., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 5:23)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #76 "Servants by Nature," 1839 February 2., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 5:24)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #77 "Salvation," 1839 February 9., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 5:25)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #78 "Christ on Life," 1839 March., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 5:26)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #80 "Christ," 1839 March 18., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 5:27)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #81 "Divinity of Christ," 1839 March 23., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 5:28)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #82 "Easter," 1839 March 30., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 5:29)
  - [Francis P. Lee] Sermon #83 "Funeral," [1839]., 1 page. D. (Box-folder 6:1)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #83 "Galatians 2. Chap," 1839 April 3., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 6:2)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #84 "Evidences," 1839 April 6., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 6:3)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #85 "Galatians. Third Chapter," 1839 April 10., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 6:4)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #86 "Evidences," 1839 April 14., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 6:5)
  - Francis P. Lee Lecture #88 "Galatians," 1839 [April]., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 6:6)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #89 "Galatians 4: 8-12," 1839 May 1., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 6:7)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #90 "Victory Over the World Through Christ," 1839 May., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 6:8)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #91 "Galatians 4: 12-20," 1839 May 9., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 6:9)
  - [Francis P. Lee] Sermon #94 "Whitsunday," [1839, ca. May 19]., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 6:10)
  - [Francis P. Lee] Sermon #99 "Love to Neighbour," 1839., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 6:11)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #100 "Life," 1839 June 23., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 6:12)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #101 "Indecision #3," 1839 June 29., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 6:13)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #[l]02"The Unknown God," [1839, ca. July 7]., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 6:14)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #104 "Obedience," 1839 July 19., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 6:15)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #105 "Prayer," 1839 November 9., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 6:16)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #107 "Christ on Righteousness," 1839 November 23., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 6:17)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #108 "Reasonableness of Religion," 1839 November 30., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 6:18)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #109 "Romans--No. 1," 1839 December., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 6:19)
  - Francis P. Lee sermon #111 "Trust in God," 1839 December 21., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 6:20)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #112 "Christmas and Thanksgiving in Florida," 1839 December 24., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 6:21)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #113 "Lessons of Time and Life," 1839 December 29., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 6:22)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #114 "1. John 4: 9," 1840 January 11., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 6:23)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #115 "Sin Deliberate," 1840 January 18., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 6:24)
  - [Francis P. Lee] Sermon, 1840 February 16., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 6:25)
  - [Francis P. Lee] Sermon #120 "Indecision No. 4," 1840 March 22., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 6:26)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #123 "Faith," 1840 May 3., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 6:27)
    Also includes Sermon, March 20, 1841.
  - [Francis P. Lee] Sermon #[?]6, 1840 [June 14]., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 6:28)
  - [Francis P. Lee] Sermon #128 "Infidelity," 1840 July 8., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 6:29)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #129 "Providence," 1840 July 19., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 6:30)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #131 "Responsibility for Sin," 1840 July 31., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 6:31)
  - ,Francis P. Lee Sermon. 1840 August 15., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 6:32)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #134 "Wisdom from Above," 1840 August 30., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 6:33)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #73 [sic], 1840 September 14., 2 items. Ms. (Box-folder 6:34)
    Includes M. J. Woart[?], Newburyport, to Rev. Francis P. Lee, Tallahassee, Florida, 16 July 1842, returning a copy [attached] of the sermon "The Ministry."
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #137 "Future Punishment," 1840 September 19., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 6:35)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #138 "Regeneration or Renovation," 1840 September 26., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 6:36)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #139 "A Prophecy Partly Fulfilled," 1840 September 30., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 6:37)
    Includes an addition for March 25, 1841.
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #140 "Salvation," 1840 October 4., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 7:1)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #141 "All are not Saved," 1840 October 11., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 7:2)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #142 "The Prodigal," 1840 October 18., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 7:3)
  - [Francis P. Lee] Sermon #144 "Divine Promises," 1840, Oct-Nov., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 7:4)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #146 "The Sabbath No. 1," 1840 November 17., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 7:5)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #147 "The Sabbath No. 2," 1840 November 27., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 7:6)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #149 "Stewards," 1840 December 12., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 7:7)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #[15]0"Confirmation," 1840 December 19., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 7:8)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon No. 1 [sic] "Evidences of Christianity," 1840 December 30., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 7:9)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon No. 2 [sic] "Evidences of Christianity," 1841 [January 6]., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 7:10)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon No. 3 sic "Evidences of Christianity," 1841 January 13., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 7:11)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #152 "A Prophecy Fulfilled," 1841 April 3., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 7:12)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #153 "Future State," 1841 May 29., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 7:13)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon "Dedicated to the Memory of My Only Daughter," 1841 June 19., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 7:14)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #158 "Repentance," 1841 November 23., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 7:15)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #159 "Sin," 1841 December 4., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 7:16)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #161 "Warning to Tallahassee," 1841 December 17., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 7:17)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #163 "Christianity," 1842 January 8., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 7:18)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #164 " Death and Decay," 1842 January 15., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 7:19)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #165 "Providence," 1842 January 29., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 7:20)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #167 "Consolation," 1842 March 5., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 7:21)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #173 "Christian Warfare," 1842 October 15., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 7:22)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #174 "Communion," 1842 No[vember]., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 7:23)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #175 "Way of the Fool," 1842 November 19., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 7:24)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #176 "Let us Walk Honestly as in the Day," 1842 December 3., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 7:25)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #177 "1. Cor. 4: 3," 1842 December 9., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 7:26)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #180 " They Understood None of These Things," 1843 February 25., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 7:27)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #181 "Communion in Lent," 1843 March 4., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 7:28)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #182 "Faith," 1843 March 17., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 7:29)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #186 "Let Him Deny Himself," 1843 April 29., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 7:30)
  - [Francis P. Lee] Sermon "So is the Will of God," 1843 May 13., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 7:31)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #189 "Confirmation No. 2," 1843 May 27., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 7:32)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #192 "Perfection No. 3," 1843 July [?]., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 8:1)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #196 "Temptations," 1843 August 9., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 8:2)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #[197] "Temptations," 1843 August 12., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 8:3)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #198 "Phariseeism," 1843 August 22., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 8:4)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #199 "Phariseeism," 1843 August 27., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 8:5)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #200 "Christian Slavery," 1843 August 30., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 8:6)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #183[sic] "Jesus Called a Little Child Unto Him," 1843 September 12., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 8:7)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #204 "These Shall Go Away into Everlasting Punishment: But the Righteous into Life Eternal," 1843 September 17., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 8:8)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #206 "Liberty," 1843 November 11., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 8:9)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #207 "Election," 1843 December 9., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 8:10)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #209 "Self Communion," 1843 December 19., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 8:11)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #210 "Christmas," 1843 December 24., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 8:12)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #211 "Communion," 1844 [January?]., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 8:13)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #219 "No Man Cometh Unto the Father But by Me," 1844 May 12., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 8:14)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #221 "Consideration," 1844 May 23., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 8:15)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #222 "Hasten," 1844 June 4., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 8:16)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #223 "Life," 1844 June 22., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 8:17)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #[224], 1844 June 26., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 8:18)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #225 "Lessons of Life," 1844 July 9., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 8:19)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #226 "Decision," 1844 July 24., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 8:20)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #227 "Hasty Conclusions," 1844 July 23., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 8:21)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #228 "Communion," 1844 August 1., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 8:22)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #229 "Lovingkindness of the Lord," 1844 August 10., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 8:23)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #230 "The Wrath of Man," 1844 August 14., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 8:24)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #231 "Sons of God," 1844 [August] 26., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 8:25)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #232 "Sons of God," 1844 August 31., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 8:26)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #233 "Waiting on the Lord," 1844 September 3., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 8:27)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #234 "Eagle's Flight," 1844 September 7., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 8:28)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #235 "Prayer," 1844 September 25., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 8:29)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #236 "Prayer," 1844 September 27., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 8:30)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #237 "Intercession," 1844 October 1., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 8:31)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #240 "Change of Heart," 1844 October 26., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 8:32)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #242 "Judgment.1," 1844 November 4., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 9:1)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #243 "Ask of God," 1844 November 11., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 9:2)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #244 "Sincerity," 1844 November 14., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 9:3)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #245 "Holy Spirit Grieved," 1844 November [?]., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 9:4)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #246 "Holy Spirit Grieved," 1844 November 24., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 9:5)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #247 "Mind of Christ," 1844 December 2., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 9:6)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #248 "Mind of Christ," 1844 December 8., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 9:7)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #249 "Christmas 1844," 1844 December 23., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 9:8)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #250 "The Heart and the Mind," 1845 January 9., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 9:9)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #251 "Eccles. 7: 10," 1845 February 8., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 9:10)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #254 "If I Be Wicked, Woe Unto Me," 1845 April 14., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 9:11)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #255 "My Days are Like a Shadow that Declineth," 1845 April 26., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 9:12)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #256 "Extent of Human Merit," 1845 May 10., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 9:13)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #257 "Communion," 1845 May 29., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 9:14)
  - F[rancis] P. Lee Sermon #259 "Forward," 1845 June., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 9:15)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #260 "Ex. 9: 1," 1845 June 30., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 9:16)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #261 Death of the Firstborn," 1845 July 12., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 9:17)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #263 "Deluge," 1845 August 19., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 9:18)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #264 "Christ Our Only Hope," 1845 September 24., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 9:19)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #265 "Love of God," 1845 September 30., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 9:20)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon # 266 "The Christian Soldier," 1845 October 31., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 9:21)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #267 "The Work of Christian Benevolence," 1845 November 7., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 9:22)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #268 "Advent," 1845 December 18., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 9:23)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #269 "Advent," 1845 December 19., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 9:24)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #270 "Consideration," 1846 January 3., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 9:25)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #271 "God is Made Man," 1846 January 8., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 9:26)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #272 "Altho the Fig Tree Shall Not Blossom," 1846 January 20., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 9:27)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #273 "Gal. 6: 10," 1846 January 24., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 9:28)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #275 "Communion," 1846 January 31., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 9:29)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #278 "God is Greater than Man," 18[46] February 17., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 10:1)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #279 "The Goodness and Severity of God," 1846 February 28., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 10:2)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #281, 1846 March 11., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 10:3)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #282 "Idolatry," 1846 March 14., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 10:4)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #283 "Profession and Privilege of a Christian," 1846 March 31., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 10:5)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #284 "Confidence of the Christian and Reasons For It," 1846 March 26., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 10:6)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #285 "Let Us Therefore, As Many As Be Perfect, Be Thus Minded," 1846 March 29., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 10:7)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #286 "I Will Go Down to the Grave Mourning," 1846 June 25., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 10:8)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #288 "The Groaning Creation," 1846 July 1., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 10:9)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #289 "Good Works," 1846 July 3., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 10:10)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #290 "A Daring Faith," 1846 July 14., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 10:11)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #293 "The Wages of Sin," 1846 July 23., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 10:12)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #294 "The Gift of God," 1846 July 24., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 10:13)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #296 "The Resurrection," 1846 August 8., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 10:14)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #297 "Unity of Divine Counsels," 1846 August 15., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 10:15)